The cure is just the beginning.
The Cured is a horror, drama, science fiction film directed by David Freyne.
What happens when the undead return to life?
In a world ravaged for years by a virus that turns the infected into zombie-like cannibals, a cure is at
last found and the wrenching process of reintegrating the survivors back into society begins.
Abbie, played by Elliot Page.
Senan, played by Sam Keeley.
Conor, played by Tom Vaughan-Lawlor.
Cantor, played by Stuart Graham.
Dr. Lyons, played by Paula Malcomson.
Katie, played by Lesley Conroy.
The Cured is a 2017 Irish horror drama film written and
directed by David Freyne in his feature debut film.
It stars Elliot Page, Sam Keeley, and Tom Vaughan-Lawlor, and was screened in the Special
Presentations section at the 2017 Toronto International Film Festival.
The film explores themes of infection, flashback, zombie, disease, military.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking and emotional.